when you run IntelliJ IDEA for the first
当您第一次运行IntelliJ IDEA时
time you'll see a welcome window showing
时间，您将看到一个欢迎窗口，显示
some of the easiest ways to get started
一些最简单的入门方法
you can create a brand new project
您可以创建一个全新的项目
import a project from another format
从其他格式导入项目
which might be another IDE or might be
这可能是另一个IDE，也可能是
defined by a Gradle or maven you can
您可以通过Gradle或maven定义
open an existing IntelliJ IDEA project
打开一个现有的IntelliJ IDEA项目
or check out code from a version control
或从版本控制中签出代码
system in this simple walkthrough we're
这个简单的演练中的系统
going to create a new project for Java
将为Java创建一个新项目
projects you'll need to have a JDK
JDK所需的项目
installed somewhere on your computer and
安装在计算机上的某个位置
you need to tell IntelliJ IDEA where
您需要告诉IntelliJ IDEA哪里
this is for this example I want to add a
在这个例子中，我想添加一个
Java 8 SDK so I can compile my project
Java 8 SDK，因此我可以编译我的项目
with Java 8 on the Mac Java is usually
在Mac上使用Java 8，通常是
found in library Java from here you can
从这里可以在Java库中找到
navigate to the version you want I'm
导航到您想要的版本
going to choose Java 8 update to one to
将选择Java 8更新到
one
一
the most recent version we're going to
我们要使用的最新版本
create a simple Java project so we don't
创建一个简单的Java项目，这样我们就不会
need to make any changes on this screen
需要在此屏幕上进行任何更改
for this example we're going to use a
在此示例中，我们将使用
simple template to provide our structure
提供我们结构的简单模板
and basic code now we have to choose a
和基本代码，现在我们必须选择一个
project name and select a location to
项目名称并选择一个位置
save the project files I'm going to keep
保存我要保留的项目文件
the default here we can also give a base
这里的默认值我们也可以给出一个基数
package so the code is put into the
包，以便将代码放入
correct directory and package IntelliJ
正确的目录和软件包IntelliJ
IDEA now creates your project every time
IDEA现在每次都创建您的项目
you start the IDE it will show you a tip
您启动IDE，它将向您显示提示
of the day these are really useful to
每天这些对于
get to know IntelliJ IDEA if you're new
如果您是新手，请了解IntelliJ IDEA
to it but even seasoned users will pick
它，但即使经验丰富的用户也会选择
up new information you can see IntelliJ
查阅新信息，您可以看到IntelliJ
IDEA has created a very simple Java file
IDEA创建了一个非常简单的Java文件
for us before we start coding let's take
为我们开始编码之前
a quick look around the IDE we can open
快速浏览一下我们可以打开的IDE
up more windows to see different aspects
打开更多窗口以查看不同方面
of our projects note the keyboard
我们的项目请注意键盘
shortcuts on the right which will help
右侧的快捷方式将有帮助
us navigate quickly to the views we need
我们快速导航到所需的视图
the project window is very useful for
项目窗口对于
seeing the structure of our project if I
看我的项目结构
press the scroll from source button I
从来源按钮按滚动I
can see where the file that's open in
可以看到打开文件的位置
the editor in the right is in the
右边的编辑器在
directory structure of the project
项目的目录结构
IntelliJ IDEA created a source directory
IntelliJ IDEA创建了源目录
for our Java code and the package
用于我们的Java代码和程序包
structure we asked for we can also see
我们要求的结构我们也可以看到
any libraries who are using in this case
在这种情况下使用的任何库
we're only using the Java 8 SDK and
我们只使用Java 8 SDK和
nothing else now let's see the project
现在没什么让我们看项目
settings and look at some of the common
设置并看一些常见
changes we might want to make there are
我们可能要进行的更改
a lot of settings because IntelliJ IDEA
很多设置，因为IntelliJ IDEA
is very customizable but it's also easy
是非常可定制的，但是也很容易
to find the ones you want by using the
通过使用找到您想要的
search box
搜索框
for example we can change our font
例如我们可以更改字体
settings I'm going to create a new
设置，我要创建一个新的
scheme for my custom settings so that if
我的自定义设置的方案，以便
I need to I can always change back to
我需要我可以随时更改回
the defaults we can select a new font
默认情况下，我们可以选择一种新字体
and I'm going to increase the size of
我将增加
this front so you can see more clearly
这条战线，所以您可以看得更清楚
the changes I'm making other settings
我正在进行其他设置的更改
you might want to customize especially
您可能想特别定制
if you're working in a team with coding
如果您在团队中进行编码
standards are the code style settings
标准是代码样式设置
here you can configure your default tabs
在这里您可以配置默认选项卡
your preferences for spaces in the code
您对代码中空格的偏好
and how you like the code to be wrapped
以及您希望如何包装代码
and formatted now we're going to take a
现在格式化，我们将采用
look at the project structure here you
看看这里的项目结构
can check you selected the correct SDK
可以检查您选择了正确的SDK
and also set the language level it's
并设置语言级别
possible to compile with Java 8 but only
可以使用Java 8进行编译，但仅限于
use Java 6 features for backwards
使用Java 6功能向后
compatibility for example we're going to
兼容性，例如，我们要
use a default level for our project
为我们的项目使用默认级别
now let's write some code IntelliJ IDEA
现在让我们写一些代码IntelliJ IDEA
has several types of code completion to
有几种类型的代码完成
help you
帮你
by default it make suggestions while
默认情况下，它会提出建议
you're typing to let you select the most
您输入的内容可以让您选择最多
appropriate values as soon as possible
尽快适当的值
now we've got something that compiles we
现在我们有了一些可以编译的东西
can run it of course you can run your
可以运行它当然可以运行
code from the run menu or you can use
运行菜单中的代码，也可以使用
the navigation bar and you'll see that
导航栏，您将看到
IntelliJ IDEA builds the project and
IntelliJ IDEA构建项目并
pops up a run window to show you the
弹出一个运行窗口，向您显示
output of running this code we can
运行此代码的输出，我们可以
consider slightly more complex examples
考虑稍微复杂一些的例子
as well let's change this code so that
同样，让我们​​更改此代码，以便
we print out the value of the first
我们打印出第一个的值
argument to the application now I need
现在需要应用程序的参数
to configure the arguments to this
配置参数
application so I can go to edit
应用程序，所以我可以去编辑
configurations on the run menu or do it
在运行菜单上进行配置或执行
from the navigation bar the application
从导航栏中的应用程序
I'm running should be selected and here
我正在跑步，应该在这里选择
I can pass in options to the VM or
我可以将选项传递给VM或
arguments to the program let's pass in a
该程序的参数让我们传递
string argument for the program to print
程序要打印的字符串参数
you're probably going to run your code
您可能会运行代码
fairly frequently so remember the
相当频繁，所以请记住
fastest way is to use keyboard shortcuts
最快的方法是使用键盘快捷键
in this case ctrl R for the Mac or shift
在这种情况下，对于Mac或shift键，请按ctrl R
f10 for Windows and Linux you can also
Windows和Linux的f10也可以
use the gutter icons to run or debug
使用装订线图标运行或调试
classes or methods if you prefer we can
类或方法，如果您愿意，我们可以
see our program arguments were passed
看到我们的程序参数被传递
into the application and the new message
进入应用程序和新消息
was printed take a look at the YouTube
被打印出来看看YouTube
channel for more video tutorials thanks
有关更多视频教程的频道，谢谢
for watching
观看